## **Adam Minder**

1069 Horizon Ridge • Lake in the Hills, IL • 60156 **CELL** (779) 220-1165 • **E-MAIL** adam@adamminder.com

### **PROFILE**

Driven professional with broad technical skill set. Excellent communicator from years of customer service experience skilled in interpreting and implementing client visions of new websites. Known for ability to multitask and a love of learning new skills to expand skillset. Focus on User Interface design.

### **SKILLS**

**Personal** – UI & UX Design · Responsive Design · User Training and Support · User Experience Research · Marketing assistance · Client Relations · Excel, Word & PowerPoint · VS Code · NodeJS · WordPress

**Technical** – HTML, CSS & JavaScript · jQuery · Vue.js · Webpack · Git/Github · Sass · Bootstrap, Materialize, Semantic and Bulma · DOM Manipulation · Photoshop · XD · Figma

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Web Developer, UI/UX Designer ELGIN, ILLINOIS - 2016 - PRESENT

- Designed, built and launched custom websites using several tools and technologies
- Creates websites that engage customers to enhance my client's online presence
- Created, modified and optimized webpage graphics and layouts using clean, modern CSS as well as custom logos and content using Photoshop
- Implements mobile-first websites and single page applications using a combination of technologies and methodologies

# National Accounts Marketing Coordinator ELGIN, ILLINOIS - 2015 - PRESENT

- Acts as liaison to establish and maintain a strong relationship and communication link with sales
  personnel and executives, both inside the company and with our customers and provides direct
  customer service to the largest and most prominent e-commerce leaders
- Builds product content to customer's specifications for e-commerce expansion
- Content management for existing e-commerce customers which includes reviewing customer's online assortment and providing suggested improvements to selection and merchandising
- Provides necessary marketing support to sales team and trains new hires
- Takes on a project's lifecycle from development to completion with minimal assistance from Project Manager

Department Manager, Wisted's Supermarket MARENGO, ILLINOIS - 2011 - 2015

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts, Information Technology
Southern New Hampshire University, Hooksett, NH – Currently in Progress